[{"id": 143, "question": "In 1947 a group of famous people from the art world headed by an Austrian conductor decided to hold an intemational festival of music,dance and theatre in Edinburgh. The idea was to reunite Europe after the Second World War. At the same time, the \"Fringe\" appeared as a challenge to the official festival.Eight theatre groups turned up uninvited in 1947,in the belief that everyone should have the right to perform,and they did so in a public house disused for years. Soon,groups of studentsfirstly from Edinburgh University, and later from the universities of Oxford and Cambridge,Durham and Birmingham were making the journey to the Scottish capital each summer to perform theatre by little-known writers of plays in small church halls to the people of Edinburgh. Today the \"Fringe\",once less recog...\n\nQ: Who joined the \"Fringe\" after it appeared?", "options": ["they owned a public house there", "University students.", "rusts from around the world.", "Performers of music and dance."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1382, "question": "One day a father and his rich family took his son on a trip to the country with the firm purpose to show him how poor people can be. They spent a day and a night on the farm of a very poor family. When they got back from their trip, the father asked his son, \"How was the trip?\" \"Very good, Dad!\" \"Did you see how poor people can be?\" the father asked. \"Yeah!\" \"And what did you learn?\" The son answered, \"I saw that we have a dog at home, and they have four. We have a pool that reaches to the middle of the garden; they have a creek that has no end. We have imported lamps in the garden; they have the stars. Our patio reaches to the front yard; they have a whole horizon.\" When the little boy finished, his father was speechless. The son added, \"Thanks, Dad, for showing me how poor we are!\" Isn't...\n\nQ: What's the best title of the passage?", "options": ["How rich are we?", "How poor are we?", "How happy are we?", "How sad are we?"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 87, "question": "When was the last time someone did something unexpectedly nice for you? Not someone you knew, but a total stranger? It's happened to me a few times, but two instances really stand out. A few years ago, I was dining out with a person who kept going on and on about himself, completely unaware of the fact that I was sitting there in misery . It wasn't his company that disappointed me. I was recovering from a bad grade in my study. I could have collapsed in tears right there at the table. When we picked up the check, the waitress said, \"Your meal was already paid for.\" My friend and I didn't have a clue how it happened. Then I remembered a man coming in out of the corner of my eye. He was dressed in mostly white, sat down at the bar, had a glass of wine, stayed for maybe ten minutes and then l...\n\nQ: What do you think of the man who paid for the meal?", "options": ["He was generous and warm-hearted.", "He knew the author well and always helped her.", "He showed his kindness to his girlfriend.", "He liked making fun of others."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 278, "question": "Ask a teacher to name the most annoying invention of recent years and they will often mention the mobile phone. Disturbed by the problems they create, many head teachers have ordered that pupils should keep their phones switched off at school. Others have told pupils to leave them at home. However, education researchers at The University of Nottingham believe it is time that phone bans were reassessed, because mobile phones can be a powerful learning aid, they say. Dr Elizabeth Hartnell-Young and her colleagues have reached this conclusion after studying the consequences of allowing pupils in five secondary schools to use either their own mobile phones or the new generation of 'smartphones' in lessons. During the nine-month experiment, 14- to-16-year-old pupils used the phones for a wide r...\n\nQ: Who benefited most from the project?", "options": ["Older pupils.", "Pupils who were not confident.", "Younger pupils.", "Pupils who were confident."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 638, "question": "As people have accurately observed,smiles are absent from early photographs. In 1852,for instance,a girl sat for her Daguerrotype,her head slightly turned,giving the camera an unsmiling look. She is preserved forever as a very serious girl indeed. Charles Darwin,a loving and playful parent,looks frozen in photographs. Why did our ancestors,from unknown sitters for family portraits to the great and famous,because so sad in front of the camera? The severity is everywhere in Victorian photographs. However,you don't have to look very long at these unsmiling old photos to see how incomplete the seemingly obvious answer is-that they are freezing their faces in order to keep still for the long exposure times. In Julia Margaret Cameron's Portrait of Tennyson,the poet dreams,his face a shadowed mas...\n\nQ: What is the author's attitude towards people not smiling in old photos?", "options": ["Skeptical.", "Critical.", "Neutral.", "Positive."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3383, "question": "Tayka Hotel De Sal Where: Tahua, Bolivia How much: About $95 a night Why it's cool: You've stayed at hotels made of brick or wood, but salt? That's something few can claim. Tayka Hotel de Sal is made totally of salt -- including the beds (though you'll sleep on regular mattresses and blankets). The hotel sits on the Salar de Uyuni, a prehistoric dried-up lake that's the world's biggest salt flat. Builders use the salt from the 4,633-square-mile flat to make the bricks, and glue them together with a paste of wet salt that hardens when it dries. When rain starts to dissolve the hotel, the owners just mix up more salt paste to strengthen the bricks. Green Magic Nature Resort Where: Vythiri, India How much: About $240 a night Why it's cool: Riding a pulley -operated lift 86 feet to your treeto...\n\nQ: What is the similarity of the four hotels?", "options": ["Being expensive.", "Being unique.", "Being beautiful.", "Being natural."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 197, "question": "Oliver Radtke believes Chinglish mistranslations may be fun, but are not to be made fun of. \"My message on Chinglish is: It should be conserved . It shouldn't be treated as a cheap joke for foreign tourists to laugh at but as a cultural treasure,\" said the 32-year-old multimedia designer, who frequently visited China for almost a decade before moving to Beijing in 2007. \"I'm trying to challenge the idea that there is only one type of standard English -- the English that's spoken in America or in the British Isles -- which is shortsighted, because Chinglish is already being used by millions of people to communicate with one another.\" So, since 2005, he has collected more than 5,000 examples of \"the wonderful results of an English dictionary meeting Chinese grammar\" on his website www.chingl...\n\nQ: It can be inferred that David Tool and Radtke   _  .", "options": ["disagree on Chinglish signs", "have both lived in China for nine years", "once argued face to face about Chinglish", "both have much knowledge of Chinese culture"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2339, "question": "Whales live in the ocean, but they are not fish. They are warm-blooded mammals and must have air to breathe. The babies are born alive and drink milk from the mother's body. It took millions of years for the whale to develop as it is today. Every spring groups of whales swim hundreds of kilometers to warm places to bear their young. Each group goes to the same place every year. The mothers take very good care of their babies. The fully grown whales are very gentle and playful with each other, and with humans. They \"talk\" to each other with a high noise that sounds beautiful. This\"talking\" can be heard for more than 300 kilometers in open waters. Yet humans kill over a hundred whales a day. They kill them to make whale oils and a lot of other things. Killing them is a modern business with m...\n\nQ: In the passage \"mammals\" refer to    _   .", "options": ["the animals which live in water", "the animals which have wings and feathers", "the animals which are fed on their mothers' milk", "the things which live in earth and have no backbones"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2573, "question": "The first reality TV show in the world was called Expedition Robinson and it was shown in Sweden in 1997. Half the population of the country watched the final event and a new kind of TV program was born. Two years later in Holland , the first series of Big Brother was filmed. Again, it was a great success and the final program was watched by 15 million people. Now more than 20 countries around the world have Big Brother or Expedition Robinson on their TV screens. The ordinary people who take part in the programs are known by millions of people in their own countries and reality TV has become big, big business. For the TV producers, reality TV is a dream come true because many of the programs cost nothing to make. At some point, the television viewers are asked to telephone the program to v...\n\nQ: It can be concluded from the passage that   _  .", "options": ["everyone is happy about reality TV.", "reality TV will do well in many countries.", "all the people in Europe are in favor of reality TV", "reality TV will not be broadcast in any countries."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2373, "question": "Take That Tiger Mom In the ongoing battle between Tiger Moms, French Mamas, and everyone else who wants to know what is the best way to raise their kids, a new study adds evidence that the extreme Tiger-style may do more harm than good. Authoritarian parents are more likely to end up with disrespectful children with violent behaviors, the study found, compared to parents who listen to their kids with the goal of gaining trust. It was the first study to look at how parenting styles affect the way teens view their parents and, in turn, how they behave. The study considered three general styles of parenting. Authoritative parents are demanding and controlling while also being warm and sensitive to their children's needs. Authoritarian parents, on the contrary, are demanding and controlling wi...\n\nQ: According to the research, what kind of parenting style is likely to cause children's criminal behaviors?", "options": ["Caring parenting.", "Permissive parenting.", "Authoritarian parenting.", "Authoritative parenting."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2824, "question": "Martha had been working for Miller Laboratories for two years, but she was not happy there. Nothing significant had happened in the way of promotions or salary increases. Martha felt that her supervisor, a younger and less experienced person than she, did not like her. In fact, the supervisor often said unpleasant things to her. One day, while talking with her friend Maria, she mentioned how discouraged she was. Maria gave her the name of a cousin of hers who was director of Human Resources Department for a large chemical company. Martha called him the next day and set up an interview on her lunch hour. During the interview, Mr. Petri said, \"You're just the kind of person we need here. You're being wasted in your other job. Give me a call in a day or two. I'm sure we can find a place for y...\n\nQ: The phrase \"the last straw\" probably refers to    _   .", "options": ["the last opportunity", "the straw that saves Martha's life", "the last reminder", "the final unpleasant thing"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 476, "question": "\"Show them the money!\" That's what some people are saying for college athletes. They say students who play sports for their school should receive salaries. Top athletes should be paid because many of them practice full time, Mark Jameson argues. Rico Cannon, a former college football player, agrees. \"Nonathletes can get a job for extra spending money, but many student athletes spend so many hours in training that they don't have time to work,\" he explains. \"Shouldn't athletes be able to earn extra money too?\" The students also make money for their schools when people buy tickets to their games. The players should receive some of that cash, supporter Robbie Pokora reasons. College athletes are about honor and tradition, but they're also a business. Thanks to ticket sales, there's money for ...\n\nQ: What's the best title for the text?", "options": ["Pay to play? ---- Will it be popular with college athletes?", "College athletes make a lot of money for their schools.", "College athletes can apply for scholarships as their salaries.", "Pay to play?---- Should college athletes be paid?"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3316, "question": "In the past ten years, America's National Basketball Association (NBA) has grown increasingly dependent on the rest of the world to supply players. When Michael Jordan and Larry Bird won gold in Barcelona in 1992, the Americans were praised for teaching the world how to play basketball. This season, however, 20 percent of NBA rosters will be filled by non-Americans. NBA commissioner David Stem happily embraces the trend. On a visit to Paris in October, Stern outlined his vision for the future, which is likely to see Europe hosting NBA games by 2010. The NBA is now planning to _ . \"Our experience in China has been that it is going to be explosive in its growth,\"said Stem. The strategy (,)in China is television.\"We've made 14 deals in China with local and national networks on cable and satel...\n\nQ: When the writer talked of \"home soil\", he was referring to  _  .", "options": ["farms in the States", "native Americans", "the NBA training center", "the USA"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3419, "question": "I am a professor of sports and exercise so I often deal with nervousness in my research with sports people. Actually, most people experience nervousness at some time or another. If you are feeling anxious, my advice is to first find the cause or causes. Make a list of those things that are making you nervous and work out which ones you can do something about. Focus all of your efforts on managing the causes that you can control. Most people cannot tell the difference between controllable and uncontrollable causes, so things they can't control become a big reason for nervousness. Dealing with this is very important if people want to keep a healthy mind. Simply try to accept the uncontrollable causes of nervousness. You might be worried about the weather on a big day, an accident or an attac...\n\nQ: What is the main purpose of this passage?", "options": ["To introduce the writer's sports experience.", "To advise on how to deal with nervousness.", "To help people remember their fears.", "To explain the dangers of nervousness."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2097, "question": "A newspaper reporter's job can be very interesting.He meets all types of people and lives quite a busy life.He is _ for news all the time,then after several years he may get a desk job,and life becomes a bit more settled.Let's look at his work a little more closely.In a day he may have to interview the prime minister of a foreign country, and the next day he may be writing about a football match.Sometimes he may be so busy that he hardly has any time to sleep.And at other times he may go on for days looking out for news materials yet return empty--handed. In the beginning,a reporter has to cover a very wide field.After the early years he becomes more specialized in his work.For example,he may finaliy be asked to write only on court cases or politics or sports.Some reporters may become so s...\n\nQ: According to the passage,a reporter's work becomes dangerous when  _  .", "options": ["he is seeing a horror film", "thereis afloodora riot", "there is a football match", "there is an interview with the prime minister"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1486, "question": "\"No man is an island\" is a well-known line from John Donne's Devotion. It was written more than three hundred years ago. Even now people still agree with him. No one can live a completely lonely life. Without other people, life will become empty and sad. We all need to have friends. For some of us, although making friends is not difficult, feeling shy, we may not want to make the first move. It is also difficult at times to keep the friends we already have. There are many books about friendship, but Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, written in 1936, is the most famous. This \"how to\" book about getting along with other people became a best seller. It was later put into 28 languages. Dale Carnegie's advice seems to be simple, but can his advice help you? Do you need to...\n\nQ: We can learn from the passage that   _  .", "options": ["John Donne learned something from Dale Carnegie", "Friends are always friends", "Few people bought Carnegie's book", "The writer of this passage agrees with John Donne and Dale Carnegie"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 969, "question": "You have heard of Webster Toys. Webster's have made good, safe, interesting toys for more than a hundred years. Now we sell them, and children play with them, in countries fromprefix = st1 /New ZealandtoNorway, and fromJapantoBrazil. We are looking for someone to sell our toys in the Far East. He (or she) will be between the ages of thirty and forty. He will already have some years of selling in world markets behind him. He will speak good English, and at least one other language of the Far East. The person we are looking for will live inSingapore, and work in our office there, but he will travel for up to six months in any one year. He will know the Far East quite well already. He will know how to sell in old markets and where to find new ones. He will understand money and make more than ...\n\nQ: Children play with Webster toys   _  .", "options": ["only in countries far away from each other", "in countries all over the world", "in only four countries of the world", "everywhere except in the Far East"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1761, "question": "I'm part of the Roots & Shoots program founded by Dr. Jane Goodall. The program is intended to make and promote positive changes in the world. As Dr. Goodall says, \"What you do makes a difference, and you have to decide what kind of difference you want to make.\" In Bulgaria, where I live, homeless dogs are everywhere. Many people here turn a blind eye to them. But I cannot ignore the life of a street dog whenever I see one wandering in the street, looking for something to eat. That's why I'm no longer a food waster. When I see wasted food, I always think of a hungry dog climbing to garbage bins, searching for food that people have thrown there. When eating in a restaurant, I'm not afraid to take leftover food to feed stray cats or dogs. A week ago, I saw a homeless dog around the garbage b...\n\nQ: The author wrote the text to ask us to   _  .", "options": ["value our food", "treat dogs as our friends", "save wasted food for homeless dogs", "raise homeless dogs and cats"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2764, "question": "What is the color1 of the universe? Astronomers had not answered this question until two months ago. That is when two American astronomers reported on their study of all the light in the universe. They said that the universe would appear to the human eyes to be a light greenish color1. Karl Glazebrook and Ivan Baldry of Johns Hopkins University in Baltimore, Maryland, reported their finding in January. They presented the research at a meeting of the American Astronomical Society. They said that finding the color1 of the universe was not part of their more serious scientific research. They did it for fun. However, earlier this month, the scientists admitted making a mistake. They said their finding was much more color1ful than it should have been. They now say the light from our universe is...\n\nQ: The two scientists found the color1 of the universe by   _  .", "options": ["combining light from about 200,000 star systems", "observing at an observatory in India", "making long-term scientific research", "using computer software programs"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 428, "question": "Aqeela Asifi, who fled to Pakistan as a young woman, has spent her life teaching other Afghan refugees. For her efforts, Ms. Asifi, who is 49, has won the 2015 UNHCR Nansen Refugee Award. She also gets $100,000 to help pay for her education projects. The UNHCR Nansen Refugee Award honors extraordinary service to people who have been forced from their homes. Eleanor Roosevelt, Graca Machel and Luciano Pavarotti are some of the other winners of the award. Asifi faced many problems in Afghanistan before she fled to Pakistan. Resources were limited and education for women was discouraged. However, in Pakistan, the 49-year-old was able to bring change to her conservative Afghan community. She persuaded parents to send their daughters to school in a tent at the Kot Chandana refugee village. The ...\n\nQ: Which of the following is TRUE about Asifi's experiences?", "options": ["Before she fled to Afghanistan, she had been a teacher in Pakistan.", "Asifi succeeded in changing attitudes of Afghan refugees toward girl education.", "Asifi determined to win the award when she began to educate Afghan girls.", "All the materials needed for teaching were borrowed."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2631, "question": "Beijing (Xinhua) -- In 2010, some 108,000 people returned to the Chinese mainland from abroad, a number that had risen 56.2 percent from the previous year, according to statistics recently published by the Ministry of Education. \"For Chinese employers, a 70 percent willingness to hire overseas workers, although that is still lower than the average rate of 76 percent for Asia, is quite a high figure when compared with the past,\" said Emma, regional director of Hays in Hong Kong and the mainland, who was in charge of the survey . Company executives , she said, have recently come to prefer hiring Chinese natives who have returned home after studying or working elsewhere.Expatriates have fallen to a second choice, she said. In the past, expatriates and returned Chinese have earned three to fou...\n\nQ: What is the best title of this article?", "options": ["A fast increasing number of Chinese returned from abroad.", "Overseas workers have higher qualification than home coworkers.", "China recorded the greatest rise in wages in Asia in 2010.", "Company executives prefer native candidates to overseas Chinese."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 359, "question": "Now that America has declared a state of swine flu public health emergency, you may be asking yourself -- what am Isupposed to do? Here is a list of practical steps you can take to prepare and protect yourself and your family. 1) Know the symptoms-- Here are some of the symptoms that sound like swine flu -- fevers over 100 degrees (37.8degC), body aches, cough, runny nose, and sometimes, nausea and diarrhea . It's also useful to know if you might have had an exposure either by recent travel to Mexico, or to the areas of known cases so far in America -- specific areas of California, Texas, New York, Ohio and Kansas. Or you may have been exposed to a sick person who came from those areas. 2) Don't panic-- If you have symptoms that sound like swine flu, do not rush to hospitals. Not only is t...\n\nQ: The purpose of the writer is mainly to   _  .", "options": ["analyze the possible causes of swine flu", "tell people how to protect themselves from swine flu", "give people some information about the present situation of swine flu", "suggest some treatments for swine flu"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2156, "question": "The Haitian tsunami gave scientists a chance to find out how well vital and potentially life-saving warning systems were working. Noaa's Pacific Marine Environmental Laboratory has developed a warning system that picks up signals of tsunamis directly from the sea-floor. It is called Dart-the Deep-ocean Assessment and Reporting of Tsunamis. If seismometers detect an earthquake, the Dart buoys will determine what is happening to sea levels, and whether a big wave might be on the way. This information is then sent via satellite to a central location which can organize an alarm. Within 50 minutes of the Haiti earthquake, this system was able to issue an alarm to other countries in the Caribbean to say that a small tsunami had been caused to start, and that was unlikely to affect them. Dr Berna...\n\nQ: Which of the following can be inferred from the passage?", "options": ["The system can warn people of the coming of tsunami directly after the earthquake.", "We can't escape the danger of tsunami within 30 minutes following the earthquake.", "Each country can easily afford a tsunami warning centre though it seldom happens.", "It's worthwhile to spend money on the warning system for possible savings of lives."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3349, "question": "In cities with rent control, the city government sets the maximum rent that a landlord can charge for an apartment. Supporters of rent control argue that it protects people who are living in apartments. Their rent cannot increase; therefore, they are not in danger of losing their homes. However, the critics say that after a long time, rent control may have negative effects. Landlords know that they cannot increase their profits . Therefore, they invest in other businesses where they can increase their profits. They do not invest in new buildings which would also be rent - controlled. As a result, new apartments are not built. Many people who need apartments cannot find any. According to the critics, the end result of rent control is a shortage of apartments in the city. Some theorists argu...\n\nQ: The problem of unemployment will happen_.", "options": ["if the minimum wage is set too high", "if the minimum wage is set too low", "if the workers are unskilled", "if the maximum wage is set"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 974, "question": "Do you scream on a roller coaster ride? You slowly climb up a steep slope until an almost vertical drop, and then... Ahhhhhhhh! Thrill-seekers like me are in luck because theme parks are pushing the boundaries of technology to create the fastest, tallest, scariest roller coasters the world has ever known. Alton Towers in Britain opened the world's first 14-1oop roller coaster a few months ago, called The Smiler. Over in Abu Dhabi, Ferrari World claims to have the world's fastest one. Ferrari World's Formula Rossa ride sends out passengers from 0-240km/h in just 4. 9 seconds. During this rapid acceleration they experience G-forces only fighter pilots usually feel: Up to 4. 8G. The designer of several rides at Alton Towers, said: \"While we can stand 6-8Gs for very short periods of time, ff w...\n\nQ: What is the best title for the passage?", "options": ["The Fastest Roller Coaster", "The Smiler and G-forces", "Screaming for Fun", "The New Technology"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2345, "question": "Have you ever intended to be fully absorbed in your work but found yourself distracted by e-mail, the Internet and other things throughout the day? According to the survey made by a famous university in the USA, most people have the experience. \"People often lose their concentration when they are bored, of course, but also when they are engaged in challenging tasks,\" says Peter Bregman, the head of the survey. \"They sometimes have a feeling to escape from what's difficult or boring, so they jump out,\" he says. The part of the brain devoted to attention is connected to the brain's emotional center. Any strong emotion --quarrels with colleagues, problems at home --can interrupt our attention. Studies over the last decade have shown that too much work to do at a time can easily lead to distra...\n\nQ: According to Robert Epstein, how can we refocus on what we should do?", "options": ["Listen to rock music for some time.", "Turn to your good friends or teachers for help.", "Run around the playground for some time.", "Take a breath from time to time."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1269, "question": "The International Voluntary Service runs a number of Youth Exchanges throughout the year.Youth Exchanges give small groups of 4-5 young people the opportunity to take part in volunteering trips abroad for an average of two weeks.These young people are joined by 4-5 young people from 3-4 other nationalities and are a wonderful intercultural experience in a safe environment. Example Youth Exchanges: Youth Exchange 1 Location:Ireland Other nationalities:Ireland,Spain,Italy,Hungary Theme:Focuses on the topic of community reconstruction and community activities--exploring how local issues facing our communities are connected to global issues.The group will also learn about the eco-village as an example of a community and take part in team-building activities. Youth Exchange 2 Location:France Ot...\n\nQ: Which nationality are Youth Exchanges most popular with?", "options": ["Spain.", "Italy", "Ireland", "France"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3111, "question": "In the 1960s, people asked about your astrological sign . In the 1990s, they wanted to know your website. These days, having a web address is almost as important as a street address. Your website is an electronic meeting place for your family, friends and potentially, millions of people around the world. Best of all, you may not have to spend a cent. The Web is filled with all kinds of free services and all it takes is some time and creativity. Think of your home page as the starting point of your website. Like the table of contents of a book or a magazine, the home page is the front door. Your site can have one or more pages, depending on how you design it. While web pages vary greatly in their design and content, most use a traditional magazine layout. At the top of the page is a banner ...\n\nQ: The writer thinks that if you are too ambitious at the beginning,   _  .", "options": ["your website may leave no space for adding new things", "you may never have your website working", "you may have no idea how to build your website", "you may tire yourself out"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2697, "question": "BERLIN---A German woman, fearful that a burglar was trying to break into her second -storey apartment, called police after she heard someone climbing up to her balcony shortly after midnight, police said Thursday. Police discovered the \"burglar\" was a man carrying flowers and a bottle of wine who turned out to be the woman's boyfriend. But then arrested him on an outstanding reason. \"He was trying to surprise her with the flowers and a bottle of wine but it all went wrong,\" said Korbach police spokesman Volker Koenig. He said the man jumped down from the balcony and tried to escape but was quickly caught by police. \"He gave the police who were taking him to jail the bottle of wine as a gesture of thanks for the friendly treatment after the arrest. \" Koenig said. LONDON---A smoker who died ...\n\nQ: The best title for the first news item might be \"  _  .\"", "options": ["A burglar's love", "A burglar boyfriend", "Flowers and wine", "Price for being romantic"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1288, "question": "Not having done physical exercise for some time, I found myself a little low-spirited and couldn't study efficiently, so I decided to do some running the next day. At 6:15 the next morning, my alarm clock rang. Unwilling to rise from my bed, I turned it off and went back to sleep. However, 5 minutes later, I struggled to get up. After washing and brushing, I had my sneakers on and went out. Wow! The air was so fresh that I couldn't help breathing it deeply. I stretched my arms and legs, then started to run. I found all things around me were so attractive. Look, the branches were waving, as if they were welcoming me; the blossoming flowers were bowing, with shyness, just like girls. Listen, the wind was whispering, as if to say \"come on, girl\". What's more interesting was those two birds, p...\n\nQ: The purpose of the writer in writing this passage is to tell us that   _  .", "options": ["the nature in the morning is very beautiful", "fresh air is beneficial", "we should appreciate the beautiful things in life", "physical exercise is useful"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 391, "question": "We've all felt discouragement at one point or another in our lives. However, when this emotion bleeds into other aspects of our life, it can sometimes be inappropriate or even harmful. I was personally discouraged by an adult during my high school. After telling her what university I wanted to attend, she plainly told me I would not get in. I was completely shocked and angry at her statement. The adult may have not intended to hurt me with her words, but it had an after effect. The meeting made me think she had no belief that I could possibly succeed in the future. After that it caused me to try to avoid any future meeting with adults until absolutely necessary. We are all human; therefore, we can all understand that some days are more challenging. But when people allow situations of stres...\n\nQ: The writer once tried to avoid meetings with adults because   _  .", "options": ["he was very busy", "he thought highly of himself", "he was once hurt by an adult", "he couldn't get high marks at school"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1734, "question": "Throughout July 1945, the Japanese mainland, from Tokyo on Honshu northward to the coast of Hokkaido, were bombed as if an invasion were about to take place. In fact, something far more threatening was at hand, as the Americans were telling Stalin at Potsdam. In 1939 physicists in the United States had learned of experiments in Germany showing the possibility of atomic power and understood the coming damage of an atomic bomb. On August 2, 1939, Albert Einstein warned President Roosevelt of the danger of Nazi Germany's advances in development of the atomic bomb. Eventually, the U.S. Office of Scientific Research Development was created in June 1941 and given combined responsibility with the War Department in the Manhattan Project to develop a nuclear bomb. After four years of research and d...\n\nQ: Albert Einstein warned Roosevelt of   _  .", "options": ["Nazi Germany' success in making an atomic bomb", "the possibility of atomic power from Nazi Germany", "Japan's unsatisfactory reply to the Allies' Potsdam Declaration", "destruction of everything from the explosion of the atomic bomb"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1713, "question": "Healthy relationships are fun and make you feel good about yourself. The relationships that you make in your teenage years will be a special pan of your life. They will teach you some of the most important lessons about who you are. This may help you understand different kinds of relationships, what makes each relationship special, and how to communicate in a positive way. What makes a relationship healthy? Communication and Sharing: The most important part of any healthy relationship between two people is being able to talk and listen to each other. You and the other person can find out what your common interests are. You can share your feelings with the other person and trust that he or she will be there to listen to you and support you. In healthy relationships, people don't lie. Commun...\n\nQ: The lessons you learn about the relationships in your teenage years may help you understand the following EXCEPT   _  .", "options": ["different kinds of relationships", "different kinds of people and occasions", "how to communicate in a positive way", "what makes each relationship special"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2906, "question": "Pulling heavy suitcases all day in the summer is hard work, especially when you are a thin 14-year-old boy. That was me in 1940-the youngest and smallest baggage boy at New York City's Pennsylvania Railway Station. After just a few days on the job, I began noticing that the other fellows were overcharging passengers. I'd like to join them, thinking, \"Everyone else is doing it.\" When I got home that night, I told my dad what I wanted to do. \"You give an honest day's work,\" he said, looking at me straight in his eye. \"They are paying you. If they want to do that, you let them do that.\" I followed my dad's advice for the rest of that summer and have lived by his words ever since. Of all the jobs I've had, it was my experience at Pennsylvania Railway Station that has stuck with me. Now I teach...\n\nQ: The writer can't put up with stealing because he thinks that   _", "options": ["it is a total shared experience", "it is considered as the most dangerous", "it does great harm to human relationship", "it may led to the loss of his sports team."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2247, "question": "Drownings, bicycle injuries, falls, and pedestrian accidents are the most common causes of childhood injury or death. Here's what you need to know to avoid tragedy: * Drowning: Each year, thousands of children die from drowning, with two-thirds of accidents occurring in the summer. To protect kids, parents should install multiple layers of protective devices, with each layer offering another opportunity to avoid a tragedy. Fences, door alarms, pool covers are all somewhat effective individually, but their effectiveness is increased dramatically when used in combination with one another. * Falls: Falls from heights kill 140 children under the age of 15 each year in the United States, and seriously injure three million more, making falls the leading cause of non-deadly injury for this age gr...\n\nQ: The passage is most probably taken from the column of   _   in a newspaper.", "options": ["social science", "technology", "entertainment", "public safety"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 857, "question": "In the decade of the 1970s, the United Nations organized several important meetings on the human environment to study a very serious problem.We humans are destroying the world around us.We must learn to protect them, or life will be very bad for our children and grandchildren. There are several major aspects to this problem. Population Most problems of the environment come from population growth.In 1700 there were 635 million people in the world; in 1900 there were 1.6 billion; in 1950, 2.5 billion; and in 1980, 4.4 billion.In the year 2010 there will be 7.3 billion.More people need more water, more food, more wood, and more petroleum. Distribution Scientists say there is enough water in the world for everyone, but some countries have a lot of water and some have only a little.Some areas g...\n\nQ: According to the passage, our world is being destroyed mainly because   _  .", "options": ["pollution is getting worse and worse", "population are increasing greatly", "we humans are using up all of our natural resources", "distribution is not reasonable."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 615, "question": "My parents knew their wealth: each other, their six children, and their faith. They tried to live simple lives so that they could have time for what was most important. They didn't busy themselves buying a bigger house, because that would mean working harder to pay the monthly mortgage ,working overtime or taking second job. Who would go running with me then? Who would read stories to me? They didn't burden themselves with buying an expensive car because that would mean worrying about installment bills. Besides, walking to the shopping centre every Saturday afternoon with me gave my dad his needed exercise, and made me feel so special. One of my heart's delights was seeing Dad and Mom in their bedroom at night, after our nightly family prayer. The lights were turned off, and I'd see the fi...\n\nQ: Which of the following is TRUE about the author's family?", "options": ["There were six people in the family.", "They decided to buy a bigger house.", "They lived an easy and happy life.", "They had a second-hand car."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3455, "question": "\"Who does the cooking in your home?\" I'm often asked by my colleagues. \"My wife and I share it 50/50,\" I usually say without hesitation. It's a lie, of course. We're pretty much even when it comes to the children and the elderly. But the paying of bills isn't 50/50-my wife pays all sorts of household expenses, so I never even have to set eyes on them. And the cooking isn't 50/50, either. The truth is that I am the cook. On my recent 40th birthday, I received the following gifts from my children: a new pot, two mini bottles of truffle oil, a decorative salad-dressing pourer, and a juice-making machine. For a moment I longed for something more manly, a cricket bat, perhaps, and then had to admit that all these things would be useful for me. It's not that my wife can't or doesn't like to cook...\n\nQ: The gifts that the writer received on his 40th birthday show that  _  .", "options": ["his children don't know him at all", "he is in charge of the cooking at home", "he doesn't get along well with his children", "his children have made wrong choices"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2678, "question": "Tokyo University laboratory has developed a robot that never loses at the game of Rock Paper Scissors. That is because its visual processing abilities and fingers work together faster than any human brain. A video of the undefeated robot has been watched by more than 3 million viewers on YouTube since going online at the end of June. Tokyo University engineering professor Masatoshi Ishikawa has a good-natured response to frustrated human losers who accuse him of essentially creating a robot that cheats. \"It is not cheating. Every one millisecond the image processor decides and recognizes the shape the human hand is going to make. And then the robot can make a winnable shape one millisecond later than a human being. Only one millisecond, but a human cannot see this difference because the hu...\n\nQ: What brings the robot so much attention on the YouTube?", "options": ["It never loses in the game against humans.", "Its eyes and fingers can work at the same time.", "It can do anything whatever people tell it to do.", "It plays online games much better than any human."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 33, "question": "What does it mean to say that we live in a world of persuasion? It means that we live among competing interests. Your roommate's need to study for an exam may take priority over pizza. Your instructor may have good reasons not to change your grade. In such a world, persuasion is the art of getting others to give fair and favorable consideration to our points of view. When we persuade, we want to influence how others believe and behave. We may not always _ -- other points of view may be more persuasive, depending on the listener, the situation, and the merit of the case. But when we practice the art of persuasion, we try to ensure that our position receives the attention it deserves. Some people, however, object to the very idea of persuasion. They may regard it as an unwelcome interruption...\n\nQ: The passage mainly discusses   _  .", "options": ["that people persuade to get what they want", "that people persuade in different ways", "that persuasion is widely accepted and appreciated", "that persuasion is important and it is all around us"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1939, "question": "Mary went out at night. She never forgot the night when she met a robber many years ago. That evening, she was invited to a birthday party which lasted until two o'clock in the morning. Without company Mary walked along the quiet street. Suddenly from the shadow of a dark building a tall man with a sharp knife in his right hand ran out at her. \"Good evening, lady,\" the man said in a low voice, \"I don't think you wish to die here.\" \"What do you want?\" Mary asked. \"Your earrings .Take them off!\" Slowly Mary's eyes looked down. She tried to cover her necklace with the collar of her overcoat while she used the other hand to take off both of her earrings, and then she quickly threw them on the ground. \"Take them and let me go.\" she said. The robber looked at her only feeling uncertain. He saw t...\n\nQ: The party   _  .", "options": ["didn't end at two", "ended before two", "lasted two hours", "was over at two"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 780, "question": "The Pew report,which was based on surveys carried out in Britain,France,Germany, Italy,Spain,Greece, Poland and the Czech Republic,said that the European Union was \"the new sick man of Europe\".The percentage of Europeans with a good view of the EU has fallen from 60 percent last year to 45 percent now. The UK may be considered the most Eurosceptic country ,but its support for the Union has barely changed in the past 1 2 months,falling only two points to 43 percent.But,France's backing for the EU has fallen sharply,from 60 percent last year to 41 percent today. On the question of whether to remain in the EU, 46 percent of the British want to leave the Union and surprisingly,the same percentage want to stay. The Pew report's authors said, \"The long-term economic crisis has created bad forces...\n\nQ: According to the passage,what's the relationship between France and Germany?", "options": ["Friendly.", "Optimistic.", "Tense.", "Simple."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3000, "question": "The hardworking blacksmith Jones used to work all day in his shop and so hard working was he that at times he would make the sparks fly from his hammer. The son of Mr. Smith, a rich neighbor, used to come to see the blacksmith everyday and for hours and hours he would enjoy himself watching how the blacksmith worked. \"Young man, why don't you try to learn to make shoe tacks , even if it is only to pass the time?\" said the blacksmith. \"Who knows, one day, it may be of use to you.\" The lazy boy began to see what he could do. But after a little practice he found that he was becoming very skilled and soon he was making some of the finest tacks. Old Mr. Smith died and the son because of the war lost all his goods. He had to leave home and settled down in another country. It so happened that in ...\n\nQ: What can we learn from the young Mr. Smith's success?", "options": ["It is no use crying over the spilt milk.", "A friend in need is a friend indeed.", "All roads lead to Rome.", "Seeing is believing."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3352, "question": "Willie Stewart still remembers his first day of kayaking through the grand Canyon. He was getting bounced around in the roughest white water he had ever seen. There was nothing the river threw at him. There he was in a 40-pound boat, with only a few months of training and one arm. Tied to his left shoulder was a prosthetic limb that he'd had for just about a week. The plan was to paddle for 20 days over 227 miles of the roughest white water in the United States. It was one of the most remarkable adventures that the Grand Canyon had ever seen. It started with a casual phone call in the spring of 2005. A good friend, Mike Crenshaw, finally got a permit from the National Park Service to lead a private party of 16 boaters down the Colorado River that coming August. He had a slot open for Willi...\n\nQ: From the passage we can know that   _  .", "options": ["Stewart was depressed at one time", "Stewart lost his left arm 22 years ago", "Stewart never complained about the unfairness of life", "Stewart was persuaded to kayak through the Grand Canyon"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 565, "question": "Culture helps human societies survive in changing natural environment.For example, the end of the last Ice Age, beginning about 15,000 years ago, brought a big challenge to which humans had to adapt.Before this time, large parts of the northern hemisphere were covered in great sheets of ice that contained much of the earth' s water.In North America, large animals that wandered the vast tundra provided people with food and materials for clothing and simple shelters.When the earth became warm, large Ice Age animals disappeared, and many land areas were covered by rising sea levels from melting ice.But people survived, they developed new technologies and learned how to survive on new plant and animal species. Finally some people settled into permanent villages, durable houses and farms. Cultu...\n\nQ: Which of the following can be the best tide of the passage?", "options": ["Natural Environment Should Be Protected.", "The Success of Cultural Adaptation Is Not Permanent.", "The Global Population Is Increasing Since Ice Age.", "Human Beings Are Capable of Surviving on Earth."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 130, "question": "This girl is almost without shelter. She may not realize it, but she's more exposed to the world than she's ever likely to be again. And it isn't because she's a girl. It could be a boy. It could be you. But why is she 'shelter less ? She s got a place to live in quite a pleasant place by the look of it and if shelter . Doesn't' t mean a house, then what does it mean? When we say someone \"lives a sheltered life\" , we don't only mean that their house is comfortable. We mean that they're protected from too many worries and troubles, that they live in a settled home, probably surrounded by friends and family, and that they don't have to cope with the difficulties the world is full of alone. Certainly no one would say that this girl was leading a sheltered life; she's leaving home to earn her ...\n\nQ: It can be inferred from the passage that this girl   _  .", "options": ["has nowhere to live", "will have problems because she's a girl", "is probably going to feel lonely", "wants to live in her home again"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2135, "question": "When my son was just learning to talk, I carried him around the house in my arms and pointed out things to him. \"Look, David, a clock. \"He'd smile and point as I did and say \"clock\". David was quick at connecting the shape of things to their words. When my son was about four years old, I walked with him to the backyard. I knew that there was an ant colony under one of the slate stones in the walkway near the shed, so I said to David, \"Come on. I want to show you something. \" As I showed David the ants that were crawling around the slate stone, he crouched down on his legs and looked with great intensity at the ants. For days after that, David wanted to look under every rock in the garden, and we often found worms, ants and so on. I recognized that David loved to look at things closely and ...\n\nQ: The author wrote the passage to   .", "options": ["recall the happy times he spent with his son", "tell us that children are full of curiosity", "tell us how to let children love nature", "advise us to develop children's interest or talent"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3101, "question": "One of India's great economic advantages is the youth of its population. To make the most of this advantage, India's children need to be educated. On paper, India is doing well here. The country has a nationwide network of state primary schools funded by a specially designed tax. 96% of children aged 6-14 go to school, even in rural areas. That's well above the average for the developing world and their attendance is good. But the attainment is poor: three quarters of third graders can't read a gradeone text and 53% of grade five kids can't read at the standard they should have achieved at grade two. Levels of achievement are almost as bad in math. \"The main problem in India is not school entry or whether there is a local school; it's the delivery of education, the way teaching is done or ...\n\nQ: Who are to blame for India's poor education according to Vinati Sukhdev?", "options": ["School teachers.", "Local governments.", "Parents with stereotypes.", "Educational organizations."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2212, "question": "Homemade Ice Cream in a Bag Difficulty: Very Easy Average User Rating:(4.3/5) Milk can become homemade ice cream in five minutes by using a bag! This homemade, creamy treat is a summertime delight for your kids and you alike. What you'll need: 1 tablespoon of sugar; 1/2 cup of milk; 1/4 teaspoon of vanilla ; 6 tablespoons of rock salt; 1 small-sized plastic food storage bag; 1 gallon-sized plastic food storage bag; ice cubes. How to make it: l Fill the large bag half full of ice, and add the rock salt. Seal the bag. l Put milk, vanilla, and sugar into the small bag, and seal it. l Place the small bag inside the large one, and seal it again carefully. l Shake until the mixture turns into ice cream, which takes about five minutes. l Wipe the top of the small bag, and then open it carefully. ...\n\nQ: Which of the following things is NOT included in both recipes?", "options": ["Sugar", "Ice", "Plastic bag", "Nuts"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2874, "question": "Both are so much related to each other. And both are so dissimilar! What are the differences between friendship and love? Is platonic friendship possible between persons of opposite sex? Let us try and understand. What is friendship? Why do we call a person our friend? When do we call someone a very good friend? If we care for a person, if we are always ready to help that person and if we share most of our thoughts with a person, they are our good friends. We can always count upon our good friends in an emergency. We are always sure that our friend will understand why we acted in a certain way. We need not explain anything to our very good friends. The friendship is so deep and the relationship is so close, that most of the things are automatically understood by our friends. What about lov...\n\nQ: The writer gives us the article to   _  .", "options": ["tell us the meaning of love and friendship.", "tell us relationship between friends and relatives.", "tell us the difference between love and friendship.", "tell us how to get friendship and love."], "answer": 2}]